feelunique.com 2012-12-27

# feelunique.com Privacy and Cookies Policy - feelunique.com

feelunique.com is a Comodo Secure Site. To ensure that this is a legitimate Comodo secure site, please check the following:

1\. That the original URL you are visiting comes from www.feelunique.com.   
2\. The status of the server certificate is valid, by clicking on one of the Comodo logos displayed on the site.

### Privacy Policy Statement

This document sets out the privacy and cookies policy of thebigwebsite Limited (trading as [feelunique.com](http://www.feelunique.com/)) ("we"/"us" and "our") and explains how we use your personal information (meaning any information about you which is personally identifiable such as your name, address, telephone number or email address and is generally referred to throughout this policy as "Your Information") collected through www.feelunique.com (the "Website"). This Privacy Policy together with our [terms](http://www.feelunique.com/content/terms) of use sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. 

### Who are We?

thebigwebsite Limited (trading as feelunique.com) is a company registered in Jersey under registration number 90552 and our registered address is Unit 9, St Peters Technical Park, St Peter, Jersey, United Kingdom, JE3 7ZN. thebigwebsite Limited is registered as a data controller. Our registration number on the register of data controllers maintained by the Jersey Information Commissioner is 15757.

### Information We Collect

We may collect and process the following data about you: 

  * details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfillment of your orders;
  * information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website or information that you otherwise provide to us. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Website (including your email address, name, address and/or telephone number) or requesting further information. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site;
  * if you contact us we may keep a record of that correspondence.

### How We Use Your Information

We use your information in the following ways: 

  * to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and your computer;
  * to provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes; 
  * to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us;
  * to notify you about changes to our service;
  * if you do not want us to use your data in this way please update your marketing preferences by contacting us at [care@feelunique.com](mailto:care@feelunique.com);

### Cookies

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system information and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patters and does not identify any individual. 

For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our site and deliver a better and more personalised service. They enable us to: 

  * estimate our audience size and usage pattern;
  * store information about your preferences and so allow us to customise our site according to your individual interests;
  * speed up your searches;
  * recognise you when you return to our site

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. If you want to know more about cookies and how they work, please refer to the following websites: [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/)

### Will We Share Your Information With Third Parties?

We may disclose your information to third parties: 

  * if we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose our personal data to the prospective buyer or seller of such business or assets;
  * if thebigwebsite Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by thebigwebsite Limited will be one of the transferred assets;
  * if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our [terms](http://www.feelunique.com/content/terms) of use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of thebigwebsite Limited, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

### Will We Transfer Your Information Overseas?

The information that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or one of our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the fulfillment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

### Data Security

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted. We use 256-bit SSL Software to encrypt your payment card information when you place an order on our secure server. For your added security all payment transactions are processed automatically by [Barclaycard SmartPay](http://www.barclaycard.com/smartpay/en/), and we are not party to your personal credit card or bank details. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

The security of personal data is important to us. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will take all reasonable measures to ensure the security of your data we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access. 

### Changes to this Privacy and Cookies Policy

We are constantly looking for new ways to improve this Website. We may amend this Privacy and Cookies Policy from time to time. All such changes will take effect once they have been posted on the site and you will be deemed to have accepted any such changes by your use of the site from time to time. This Privacy and Cookies Policy was last updated on 27/12/2012

### How to contact us

Please contact us if you have any questions regarding this Privacy and Cookies Policy or about any information we hold about you by emailing us at [care@feelunique.com](mailto:care@feelunique.com). You can also send a letter by mail to: feelunique.com, St Peters Technical Park, St Peter, Jersey, United Kingdom, JE3 7ZN

You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of the information we hold about you, please contact us at [care@feelunique.com](mailto:care@feelunique.com), feelunique.com, St Peters Technical Park, St Peter, Jersey, United Kingdom, JE3 7ZN. We may make a charge of £10 for this.

We want to make sure that Your Information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate by contacting us at [care@feelunique.com](mailto:care@feelunique.com), feelunique.com, St Peters Technical Park, St Peter, Jersey, United Kingdom, JE3 7ZN;

You have the right to ask us not to use Your Information for marketing purposes. To change your marketing preferences, or to unsubscribe, please contact us at [care@feelunique.com](mailto:care@feelunique.com).

We hope that you will be happy with the way we handle your information. You always have the right to complain to the Information Commissioner in relation to our activities – for more information visit www.dataprotection.gov.je
